Harold Stein Filk Collection
Harold Stein Filk Archive
Harold Stein Filk Collection
1960-2020
Harold Stein Filk Archive
filk
34 boxes and an unknown number of terrabytes
Harold Stein was an active member of the Filking community. He amassed a large collection of filk songs, zines, convention papers, and audio recordings.
Scope and Content
The Harold Stein Filk Collection contains....
General
The Harold Stein Filk Collection contains....
Access
The collection is open and available for research.
Filk Music
- Conventions
  - Albacon
    - Albacon 2008, 10 Oct 2008 to 12 Oct 2008
      Albany, NY
      - Albacon 2008 Friday Night Open Filk Disk 1 of 3 10/08, 1 October 2008; Notes: Origin: Convention: Albacon 2008; Burnt DVD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
        Convention--Albacon 2008; Burnt DVD
      - Albacon 2008 Sat Night Open Filk Disc 2 of 3 10/08, 1 October 2008; Notes: Origin: Convention: Albacon 2008; Burnt DVD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
      - Albacon 2008 Rebecca Angel Concert Disc 3/3 10/08, Notes: Origin: Floating Filk Studios Convention: Albacon 2008; Burnt CD 1 copy; Albacon; Floating Filk Studios (Box Somewhere safe (Possibly Box CC))
        Albacon; Floating Filk Studios; Various; Floating Filk Studios; Convention--Albacon 2008; Burnt CD
  - Archon
    - Archon 35, 30 Sep 2011 to 02 Oct 2011
      Collinsville, IL
      - Archon 35 Filk Book, 2011; Notes: Blue cover with chthulu playing guitar, John Sies, cover art. Cat Morrese and Bari Greenberg did the layout Origin: Convention: Archon 35; Songbook 1 copy (Box Box #13 (K))
        various; Convention--Archon 35; Songbook
      - Archon 35 Filk Book, 2011; Notes: Blue cover with chthulu playing guitar, John Sies, cover art. Cat Morrese and Bari Greenberg did the layout Origin: Convention: Archon 35; Songbook 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
    - Archon 36, 12 Oct 2012 to 14 Oct 2012
      - Archon 36 Filk Book, 2012; Notes: Layout by Sandra and Bari Greenberg, cover has the Orion Nebua. Spiral bound, glossy book Origin: Convention: Archon 36; Songbook 2 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
        Convention--Archon 36; Songbook
    - Archon 39, 02 Oct 2015 to 04 Oct 2015
      - Archon 39 Songbook, 2014; Notes: Produced for Archon 38 Origin: Convention: Archon 39: 2015; Songbook 4 copy; Archon 39, 2014 (Box Box #09 (N))
        Archon 39, 2014; Convention--Archon 39: 2015; Songbook
      - Archon 39 Songbook, 2015; Notes: Produced for Archon 38 Origin: Archon 39, 2015 Convention: Archon 39: 2015; Songbook 2 copy; Archon 39 (Box Box #09 (N))
        Archon 39; Archon 39, 2015; Convention--Archon 39: 2015; Songbook
      - Archon 39 Filk Book, 2015; Notes: White cover with arches Origin: Mountain Cat Media Convention: Archon 39; Songbook 1 copy (Box Box #13 (K))
        various; Mountain Cat Media; Convention--Archon 39; Songbook
    - Archon 40, 29 Sep 2017 to 01 Oct 2017
      - Archon 40 Songbook, 2016; Notes: Produced for Archon 40, Spiral bound Origin: Convention: Archon 40: 2017; Songbook 2 copy; Archon 40, 2016 (Box Box #09 (N))
        Archon 40, 2016; Convention--Archon 40: 2017; Songbook
    - Archon 41, 29 Sep 2018 to 01 Oct 2018
      - Archon 41 Filk Book, 2017; Notes: Blue cover with with abstract shapes and rocket, Katrina Joyner, cover art. Cat Greenberg did the layout, Loose song Falcon Nine is tucked into the book Origin: Mountain Cat Media Convention: Archon 41: 2018; Songbook 2 copy (Box Box #13 (K))
        various; Mountain Cat Media; Convention--Archon 41: 2018; Songbook
  - Arisia
    - Arisia 2008, 18 Jan 2008 to 21 Jan 2008
      Boston, MA
      - Arisia 2008 Saturday Night Open FIlk, Notes: Contains truncated files due (we think) to the file writing system Harold was using having a 2 GB limit. The files are still readable to that point, thank Ghu. Origin: Floating Filk Studios Convention: Arisia 2008; Burnt CD 1 copy; Arisia 2008; Floating Filk Studios (Box Somewhere safe (Possibly Box CC))
        Arisia 2008; Floating Filk Studios; Various; Floating Filk Studios; Convention--Arisia 2008; Burnt CD
      - Arisia 2008 Sunday Night Open Filk, Notes: Contains truncated files due (we think) to the file writing system Harold was using having a 2 GB limit. The files are still readable to that point, thank Ghu. Origin: Floating Filk Studios Convention: Arisia 2008; Burnt CD 1 copy; Arisia 2008; Floating Filk Studios (Box Somewhere safe (Possibly Box CC))
  - Balticon
    - Balticon 26, 17 Apr 1992 to 19 Apr 1992
      Baltimore, MD
      - Balticon 26 Chaos Filk, Notes: label only on tape; from Eli G Origin: Convention: Balticon 26; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #25 (II))
        Convention--Balticon 26; Tape
      - Balticon Filkbook, 1992; Notes: Yellow cover with squirrel and several marks on tree Origin: Convention: Balticon 26; Songbook 1 copy (Box Box #16 (Z))
        various; Convention--Balticon 26; Songbook
    - Balticon 27, 09 Apr 1993 to 11 Apr 1993
      Hunt Valley, MD
      - Fri Concerts 1993 Balt, Notes: label only on tape; from Eli G Origin: Convention: Balticon 27: 1993; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #25 (II))
        Convention--Balticon 27: 1993; Tape
    - Balticon 38, 28 May 2004 to 31 May 2004
      - BLTCN - 3 Balticon 2004 Disc 3, Notes: Mini - 005 fifth box of minidiscs #6 Origin: Convention: Balticon 38: 2004; MiniDisc 1 copy (Box Box #17 (AA))
        Convention--Balticon 38: 2004; MiniDisc
      - Balticon 2004 - 1 Discs 1-3, Notes: Mini - 005 fifth box of minidiscs #4 Origin: Convention: Balticon 38: 2004; MiniDisc 1 copy (Box Box #17 (AA))
      - Balticon BL - Disc 2, 2004; Notes: Mini - 005 fifth box of minidiscs #5 Origin: Convention: Balticon 38: 2004; MiniDisc 1 copy (Box Box #17 (AA))
    - Balticon 44, 28 May 2010 to 31 May 2010
      - SSDWC: Geek Pantheon, 2010; Notes: Kim's card inside the CD case Origin: http://comicbookgoddess.com Convention: Balticon 44: 2010; Commercial CD 1 copy; Fortuner, Kimberley (Box Box #03 (I))
        Fortuner, Kimberley; Fortuner, Kimberley; http://comicbookgoddess.com; Convention--Balticon 44: 2010; Commercial CD
    - Balticon 47, 24 May 2013 to 27 May 2013
      - Sundown - Whispers of Ragnarok: Norse Myth Song Cycle, 2014; Notes: Origin: Ada Palmer Convention: Balticon 47: 2013; Commercial CD 1 copy; Sassafras; Ada Palmer (Box Box #05 (J))
        Sassafras; Ada Palmer; Sassafrass; Ada Palmer; Convention--Balticon 47: 2013; Commercial CD
      - Sundown: Whispers of Ragnarok, 2013; Notes: Origin: Ada Palmer Convention: Balticon 47: 2013; Commercial DVD 1 copy; Sassafras; Ada Palmer (Box Box #05 (J))
        Sassafras; Ada Palmer; Sassafrass; Ada Palmer; Convention--Balticon 47: 2013; Commercial DVD
    - Balticon 51, 26 May 2017 to 29 May 2017
      - Balticon 51 - Baltimore Science Fiction Society, 2017; Notes: Yellow flier, double sided Origin: May 26-29, 2017 Convention: Balticon 51; Flier 1 copy (Box Box #09 (N))
        May 26-29, 2017; Convention--Balticon 51; Flier
  - BayFilk
    - BayFilk III, 1986
      - BayFilk III Songbook: It Was Late ..., Notes: OCP-77: Light green cover with bulldozer riding over musical notes, spiral bound Origin: Convention: BayFilk III; Songbook 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
        Convention--BayFilk III; Songbook
      - Bayfilk 3: Concert Center Stage [green printing], Notes: OCP-71: case label has the wrong recording date: "Recorded Live at Bayfilk III, March 1985" Origin: Convention: BayFilk III; Professional Cassette 2 copy (Box Box #24 (HH))
        Convention--BayFilk III; Professional Cassette
      - Bayfilk 3: Concert Center Stage [handwritten label], Notes: OCP-71 Origin: Convention: BayFilk III; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #24 (HH))
      - Bayfilk 3: Concert Center Stage [white printing], Notes: OCP-71: case label lacks the (C) and (P) icons in front of the copyright year Origin: Convention: BayFilk III; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #24 (HH))
      - Bayfilk 3: Concert On Stage [bare tape], Notes: OCP-72 Origin: Convention: BayFilk III; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #24 (HH))
      - Bayfilk 3: Concert On Stage [green printing], Notes: OCP-72: tape label in black rather than purple; case label has the wrong recording date: "Recorded Live at Bayfilk III, March 1985" Origin: Convention: BayFilk III; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #24 (HH))
      - Bayfilk 3: Concert On Stage [white printing], Notes: OCP-72: case label lacks the (C) and (P) icons in front of the copyright year Origin: Convention: BayFilk III; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #24 (HH))
      - Bayfilk III Back Stage, Notes: OCP-74 Origin: Convention: BayFilk III; Professional Cassette 2 copy (Box Box #24 (HH))
      - Bayfilk III Back Stage [handwritten label], Notes: OCP-74 Origin: Convention: BayFilk III; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #24 (HH))
      - Bayfilk III Stage Struck, Notes: OCP-73 Origin: Convention: BayFilk III; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #24 (HH))
      - Bayfilk III Stage Struck [bare tape], Notes: OCP-73 Origin: Convention: BayFilk III; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #24 (HH))
      - Challenger Memorial, 1986; Notes: OCP-70 Origin:: https://archive.org/details/filk_challenger_memorial Convention: BayFilk III; Professional Cassette 3 copy (Box Box #28 (LL))
      - Challenger Memorial 105, 1986; Notes: OCP-70 Origin:: https://archive.org/details/filk_challenger_memorial Convention: BayFilk III; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #28 (LL))
        Convention--BayFilk III; Tape
    - Bayfilk 4, 1988
      - Julia Ecklar - Bayfilk 4 Concert, 1 March 1988; Notes: Origin: Convention: Bayfilk 4: 1988; Tape - Home recorded cassette 1 copy (Box Box #20 (RR))
        Ecklar, Julia; Convention--Bayfilk 4: 1988; Tape - Home recorded cassette
    - Bayfilk 1, 05 Mar 1982 to 07 Mar 1982
      - BayFilk I Program and Songbook, 1982; Notes: Lime green cover with dumptruck dumping musical notes, staple bound Origin: Convention: Bayfilk 1; Songbook|Program Book 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
        Convention--Bayfilk 1; Songbook|Program Book
      - Bayfilk 1 Raw tape, Notes: label only on case Origin: Convention: Bayfilk 1; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
        Convention--Bayfilk 1; Tape
      - Bayfilk 1 not so Instant Songbook, Notes: Origin: Convention: Bayfilk 1; Songbook 1 copy (Box Box #29 (MM))
        Convention--Bayfilk 1; Songbook
      - Bayfilk Concert, Notes: OCP-10 Origin: Convention: Bayfilk 1; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #24 (HH))
        Convention--Bayfilk 1; Professional Cassette
      - Bayfilk Concert [tiny handwritten label], Notes: label only on tape; photos are of a note in the case, not the actual label, which is blank Origin: Convention: Bayfilk 1; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #23 (GG))
      - Bayfilk Crazies, Notes: OCP-15 Origin: Convention: Bayfilk 1; Professional Cassette 6 copy (Box Box #24 (HH))
      - Bayfilk I Concert + Crazies (Part 1) [tiny handwritten label], Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Bayfilk 1; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #23 (GG))
      - Bayfilk Not So Instant Songbook, 1982; Notes: Green cover with dumptruck Origin: Off Centaur Publications, 1982 Convention: Bayfilk 1; Songbook 3 copy; Bayfilk 1, 1982; Off Centaur Publications, 1982 (Box Box #10 (P))
        Bayfilk 1, 1982; Off Centaur Publications, 1982; Off Centaur Publications, 1982; Convention--Bayfilk 1; Songbook
      - Margaret Middleton at Bayfilk 1, Notes: OCP-07 Origin: Convention: Bayfilk 1; Professional Cassette 3 copy (Box Box #24 (HH))
      - The Best of Bayfilk, Notes: OCP-11 Origin: Convention: Bayfilk 1; Professional Cassette 8 copy (Box Box #24 (HH))
      - The Best of Bayfilk 1 [no liner notes], Notes: OCP-11: label only on tape Origin: Convention: Bayfilk 1; Professional Cassette 44 copy (Box Box #31 (OO))
      - BayFilk I Program and Songbook, 1982; Notes: Lime green cover with dumptruck dumping musical notes, staple bound Origin: Convention: Bayfilk 1: 1982; Songbook|Program Book 1 copy (Box Box #16 (Z))
        Convention--Bayfilk 1: 1982; Songbook|Program Book
      - Bayfilk Not So Instant Songbook, 1982; Notes: Green cover with dumptruck Origin: Off Centaur Publications, 1982 Convention: Bayfilk 1: 1982; Songbook 1 copy; Bayfilk 1, 1982; Off Centaur Publications, 1982 (Box Box #16 (Z))
        Bayfilk 1, 1982; Off Centaur Publications, 1982; Off Centaur Publications, 1982; Convention--Bayfilk 1: 1982; Songbook
      - #60 Margaret Middleton at Bayfilk 1, Notes: OCP-07: label only on case Origin: Convention: Bayfilk 1; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
        Middleton, Margaret; Convention--Bayfilk 1; Tape
      - BayFilk Albums, Notes: Origin: Commercial tapes Convention: Bayfilk 1; Burnt CD 1 copy; BayFilk (Box Somewhere safe (Possibly Box CC))
        BayFilk; Various; Commercial tapes; Convention--Bayfilk 1; Burnt CD
    - Bayfilk II, 02 Mar 1984 to 04 Mar 1984
      - #72 Bayfilk II Concert - #1, Notes: OCP-28: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Bayfilk II; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
        Convention--Bayfilk II; Tape
      - #73 Bayfilk II Concert - Volume 2, Notes: OCP-29: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Bayfilk II; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      - #74 The Best of Bayfilk II, Notes: label on tape and case; missing a few songs from the official version Origin: Convention: Bayfilk II; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #24 (HH))
      - Bayfilk #2 Julia Ecklar Tape; Julia - Darkover 1985; Julia - Darkover 1985 Myfanwy #1; Julia - Darkover 1985 Myfanwy #2; Julia - Filk Sings and Bardic Circles 1, Notes: Part of a pack - rubber banded together Origin: Convention: Bayfilk II; Burnt DVD 1 copy (Box Box #21 (D))
        Convention--Bayfilk II; Burnt DVD
      - Bayfilk II Baysong Filkbook, Notes: Origin: Convention: Bayfilk II; Songbook 1 copy (Box Box #29 (MM))
        Convention--Bayfilk II; Songbook
      - Bayfilk II Concert Volume 1, Notes: OCP-28 Origin: Convention: Bayfilk II; Professional Cassette 3 copy (Box Box #24 (HH))
        Convention--Bayfilk II; Professional Cassette
      - Bayfilk II Concert Volume 2, Notes: OCP-29 Origin:: https://archive.org/details/filk_bayfilk_ii_concert_volume_2 Convention: Bayfilk II; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #24 (HH))
      - Bayfilk II Concert Volume 2 [handwritten label], Notes: OCP-29 Origin: Convention: Bayfilk II; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #24 (HH))
      - Bayfilk II Dredgings [black ink tape], Notes: OCP-31 Origin: Convention: Bayfilk II; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #24 (HH))
      - Bayfilk II Dredgings [green ink tape], Notes: OCP-31 Origin: Convention: Bayfilk II; Professional Cassette 2 copy (Box Box #24 (HH))
      - The Best of Bayfilk II, Notes: OCP-30 Origin: Convention: Bayfilk II; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #24 (HH))
      - BayFilk II Program and Songbook, 1984; Notes: Origin: Convention: Bayfilk II: 1984; Songbook|Program Book 1 copy (Box Box #16 (Z))
        Convention--Bayfilk II: 1984; Songbook|Program Book
      - BayFilk Progress Report 2, 1994; Notes: Light grey-green pamphlet style, staple bound Origin: Off Centaur Publications Convention: Bayfilk II: 1984; Progress report 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
        Off Centaur Publications; Convention--Bayfilk II: 1984; Progress report
    - Bayfilk 5, 03 Mar 1989 to 05 Mar 1989
      - Bayfilk 5, 1989, March 3-5, Notes: Neon green cover with classical musician Schedule of events Origin: Convention: Bayfilk 5: 1989; Program booklet 1 copy (Box Box #02 (FF))
        Bayfilk 5, 1989, March 3-5; NA; Convention--Bayfilk 5: 1989; Program booklet
  - BloominCon
    - BloominCon, 1982
      - # 77 Martha & Bloomin Con 7/82, Notes: label on case; tape side A says: 'For Lois "My Friend" (C) 1982 Martha J. Bonds' Origin: Convention: BloominCon; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #25 (II))
        Convention--BloominCon; Tape
  - Boskone
    - Boskone 14, 18 Feb 1977 to 20 Feb 1977
      - Mik Ado About Nothing (Back to Rivets, part 1), Second edition, 1 August 1980; Notes: Limited edition of 250 copies. Blue cover with Cthulu in beanie with ProCon 1980 on forehead, holding a lobster Origin: Chainik Press Publications in-print (different version/edition): http://data.nesfa.org/press/Books/KellerAnderson.html Convention: Boskone 14: 1977; Musical in songbook format 1 copy (Box Box #16 (Z))
        Anderson, Sue and Kellar, Mark M.; Chainik Press Publications; Convention--Boskone 14: 1977; Musical in songbook format
      - The Boskone 14 Filkson Supplement to the NESFA Hymnal, 1977; Notes: Orangy cover with a multi-armed alien at the MIT post office. Origin: NESFA, Inc. Convention: Boskone 14; Songbook 1 copy; Boskone 14, 1977; NESFA, Inc. (Box Box #02 (FF))
        Boskone 14, 1977; Various; NESFA, Inc.; NESFA, Inc.; Convention--Boskone 14; Songbook
    - Boskone 23, 14 Feb 1986 to 16 Feb 1986
      - Boskone '86 T4, Notes: label on tape and case Origin: Convention: Boskone 23: 1986; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #25 (II))
        Convention--Boskone 23: 1986; Tape
    - Boskone 45, 15 Feb 2008 to 17 Feb 2008
      - Boskone 2008 Concerts - Seanan McGuire, Peaked Out, Gary Ehrlich (Mono + Stereo), MEW + Ed Stauff (Mono + Stereo), Song Sequitur (Mono), 2/08, 1 February 2008; Notes: Origin: Convention: Boskone 45: 2008; Burnt DVD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
        Convention--Boskone 45: 2008; Burnt DVD
      - Boskone 2008 Friday Night Open Filk 2/08, 1 February 2008; Notes: Origin: Convention: Boskone 45: 2008; Burnt DVD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
      - Boskone 45 Program book, 2008; Notes: White booklet Origin: Convention: Boskone 45; Program booklet 1 copy; Boskone 45, February 15-17, 2008 (Box Box #07 (R))
        Boskone 45, February 15-17, 2008; NA; Convention--Boskone 45; Program booklet
      - Boskone 2008 Batya and Merav concert, Crystal Paul MP3 recording, Bob Rosenfeld concert, Memorial Circle for Greg McMullen - raw + split, pictures taken at all recordings, 1 February 2008; Notes: Origin: Floating Filk Studios Convention: Boskone 45: 2008; Burnt DVD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
        Various; Floating Filk Studios; Convention--Boskone 45: 2008; Burnt DVD
      - Boskone 2008 Saturday night open filk, 1 February 2008; Notes: Origin: Floating Filk Studios Convention: Boskone 45: 2008; Burnt DVD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
    - Boskone 48, 18 Feb 2011 to 20 Feb 2011
      - 2011 Boskone Vrds, Notes: Contains Erica Neely Concert and Walk in the Day parts 1 and 2 Origin: Convention: Boskone 48: 2011; Burnt DVD 1 copy (Box Box #21 (D))
        Various; Convention--Boskone 48: 2011; Burnt DVD
    - Boskone 49, 17 Feb 2012 to 19 Feb 2012
      - Gary McGath schedule for Boskone 49, 2012; Notes: White single sided page Origin: Convention: Boskone 49: 2012; Convention Documents 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
        Convention--Boskone 49: 2012; Convention Documents
      - Helmuth: Speaking for Boskone 49, #1, 2012; Notes: Yellow paper, double sided Origin: Convention: Boskone 49: 2012; Newsletter 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
        Convention--Boskone 49: 2012; Newsletter
      - Helmuth: Speaking for Boskone 49 #2, 2012; Notes: Blue paper, double sided Origin: Convention: Boskone 49: 2012; Newsletter 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
      - Moderator guide, 2012; Notes: White single sided page Origin: Convention: Boskone 49: 2012; Convention Documents 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
      - Welcome to Boskone 49 - Program participant welcome, 2012; Notes: White single sided page Origin: Convention: Boskone 49: 2012; Convention Documents 1 copy (Box Box #14 (H))
    - Boskone 51, 14 Feb 2014 to 16 Feb 2014
      - Boskone 51, 2014; Notes: Origin: February 14-16, 2014 Convention: Boskone 51; Pocket program 1 copy (Box Box #09 (N))
        February 14-16, 2014; Convention--Boskone 51; Pocket program
      - Helmuth newsletter, Volume 51, issue 1, 2014; Notes: Friday edition Origin: Convention: Boskone 51: 2014; Newsletter 1 copy; Boskone 51, 2014 (Box Box #09 (N))
        Boskone 51, 2014; Convention--Boskone 51: 2014; Newsletter
      - Helmuth newsletter, Volume 51, issue 2, 2014; Notes: Satuday edition Origin: Convention: Boskone 51: 2014; Newsletter 1 copy; Boskone 51, 2014 (Box Box #09 (N))
      - Helmuth newsletter, Volume 51, issue 3, 2014; Notes: Saturday night edition Origin: Convention: Boskone 51: 2014; Newsletter 1 copy; Boskone 51, 2014 (Box Box #09 (N))
      - Helmuth newsletter, Volume 51, issue 4, 2014; Notes: Sunday edition Origin: Convention: Boskone 51: 2014; Newsletter 1 copy; Boskone 51, 2014 (Box Box #09 (N))
    - Boskone 52, 13 Feb 2015 to 15 Feb 2015
      - Boskone 52, 2015; Notes: Origin: Boskone 52, February 13-15, 2015 Convention: Boskone 52; Program book 1 copy; Boskone 52, February 13-15, 2015 (Box Box #09 (N))
        Boskone 52, February 13-15, 2015; Boskone 52, February 13-15, 2015; Convention--Boskone 52; Program book
      - Boskone 52 Program Book, 2015; Notes: Origin: February 13-15, 2015 Convention: Boskone 52; Program book 1 copy; Boskone 52 (Box Box #09 (N))
        Boskone 52; February 13-15, 2015; Convention--Boskone 52; Program book
      - Helmuth newsletter, Volume 52, issue 4, 2015; Notes: Sunday edition Origin: February 13-15, 2015 Convention: Boskone 52; Newsletter 1 copy; Boskone 52 (Box Box #09 (N))
        Boskone 52; February 13-15, 2015; Convention--Boskone 52; Newsletter
    - Boskone, February 15
      - Boskone Saturday Night, Notes: Featuring filkers, Sassafrass, Bill Roper, Lady Mondegreen Origin: Convention: Boskone, February 15; Program 2 copy; Boskone, February 15 (Box Box #09 (N))
        Boskone, February 15; Convention--Boskone, February 15; Program
  - British Filk Convention
    - British Filk Convention 1, Contabile, 02 Feb 1989 to 05 Feb 1989
      Newbury, UK
      - The Unofficial Contabile Tape, Notes: In cardboard box Origin: Convention: British Filk Convention 1, Contabile; Tape - Home recorded cassette 1 copy (Box Box #20 (RR))
        Convention--British Filk Convention 1, Contabile; Tape - Home recorded cassette
      - Contabile, Notes: Origin: Convention: British Filk Convention 1, Contabile: 1989; Professional Cassette 2 copy (Box Box #24 (HH))
        Convention--British Filk Convention 1, Contabile: 1989; Professional Cassette
      - Contabile 191 [copy], Notes: photocopy of the full official liner notes Origin: Convention: British Filk Convention 1, Contabile: 1989; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #24 (HH))
        Convention--British Filk Convention 1, Contabile: 1989; Tape
    - British Filk Convention 6, VIbraphone, 04 Feb 1994 to 06 Feb 1994
      - Vibrations, 1995; Notes: LORE002 Origin: Convention: British Filk Convention 6, VIbraphone; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #23 (GG))
        Convention--British Filk Convention 6, VIbraphone; Professional Cassette
    - British Filk Convention, 12 Didgeri-Douze, 04 Feb 2000 to 06 Feb 2000
      Milton Keynes
      - Chris Conway - Live!, 2001; Notes: Recorded at Didgeridouze, 12th UK Filk Convention, Milton Keynes, 4th Feb, 2000, 1, 12, 13 recorded at Conthirteena, 13th UK Filk Convention, Eastbourne, 3rd Feb 2001. Origin: @2001 A New Day Records Convention: British Filk Convention, 12 Didgeri-Douze; Commercial CD 1 copy; Conway, Chris; @2001 A New Day Records (Box Box #03 (I))
        Conway, Chris; @2001 A New Day Records; Conway, Chris; @2001 A New Day Records; Convention--British Filk Convention, 12 Didgeri-Douze; Commercial CD
    - British Filk Convention 13, Conthirteena, 02 Feb 2001 to 04 Feb 2001
      Eastbourne, UK
    - British Filk Convention 14, Contabile Fortean, 01 Feb 2002 to 03 Feb 2002
    - British Filk Convention 19, D'Zenove, 02 Feb 2007 to 04 Feb 2007
      - 2007 UK Filkcon Raw Recordings from Net 2/07, Notes: Origin: UK Filk Con soundboard feed Convention: British Filk Convention 19, D'Zenove; Burnt CD 1 copy; D'Zenove (Box Somewhere safe (Possibly Box CC))
        D'Zenove; Various; UK Filk Con soundboard feed; Convention--British Filk Convention 19, D'Zenove; Burnt CD
    - British Filk Convention 20, 2t0nic, 01 Feb 2008 to 03 Feb 2008